♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Mercado] They'll find out
that your identity yesterday was fake.
If that happens,
the embassy will be alerted.
It's either they'll lock down the embassy
or move your target.
So, you must hurry, Atoy.
[in English] Ready to execute.
[in English] My friend, how are you?
[in English] I would want you to meet
my lovely daughter, Audrey.
- [in English] Hello.
- Audrey, Viktor Petrov.
[in English] The ambassador of Zahran.
[in English] Uh, hello, Atoy.
I-I just wanted to let you know
I'm here now at the Embassy of Zahran.
[Atoy] What are you doing here
at the embassy?
I can't face Brother Atoy
because I feel guilty.
But you didn't do anything wrong.
I didn't do anything wrong,
but I'm ashamed
of how you deceived his family.
I'm not so shameless like you.
PREVIOUSLY
[in Russian] You idiot!
[in English] Get off your phone
and get back to work!
[Paldo] Sir Delfin's death anniversary
must be near.
[Cita] Delfin said when you were a child,
you were a good kid,
and he was sure
you'd grow up to be a good man.
[Victor, in English] I thought
you liked the music, Audrey.
- [in English] Why-- Why did you join us?
- [safe keys blipping]
[Audrey, in English] I just
wanna make sure that
my dad doesn't do something silly!
[in English] You have
a very protective daughter, Dmitri.
[Victor chuckles]
[safe blipping]
[door lock clicks]
[rousing music playing]
[in English] Isn't
my daughter sweet? [sighs]
[in English] She's most valuable to me.
[in English] Very protective.
[both chuckle]
[in English] Oh, I like your office.
- [in English] Very nice.
- [in English] My little home.
[in English] Everything
came from, uh, Russia?
[in English] Just about.
[in English] But this, I'm very proud of.
[suspicious music playing]
[Dmitri, in English] Tell me about it.
[Viktor, in English] Uh, this is very old.
[indistinct chattering]
[Viktor, in English]
It's very scary, actually.
[tense music playing]
[in English] Audrey,
what are you doing there?
Um… [chuckles]
[in English] She's probably admiring
my wine collection.
[in English] Oh! [chuckles]
- [in English] But…
- [in English] Yes.
[in English] I want to show
the two of you something very special.
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clacking]
[clicking]
[electronic blipping]
[music fades]
Later, when the shipment arrives,
we must all be complete.
- [in English] Yes, boss.
- It must be protected properly.
You two, at the gate.
Roger.
The rest with me.
[pensive music playing]
What kind of shipment is this?
Why must everyone be there?
We're sending more women this time.
It cannot fail.
Is there a problem, Paldo?
[anxious music playing]
Can I pass?
What?
I don't want to do this anymore.
I'm leaving the group.
Are you crazy?
- [music fades]
- You cannot leave the group!
[Red] Who's leaving?
[tense music playing]
[in English] Is that a… broken car emblem?
[in English] Yes.
[in English] That's from my first car
from my junkyard.
- [in English] You have a junkyard?
- [in Russian] Yes.
[in English] In San Rodolfo, Bulacan.
[sinister music playing]
[in English] I'm thinking of expanding,
but I have a slight problem.
[in English] I'm having
a hard time shipping the cars.
[in English] My friend,
why didn't you tell me?
[in English] I have a shipping business.
[in English] I can definitely
help you with that.
[in English] That is good!
[in English] Come, let's talk.
Please, have a--
[in English] That's not
supposed to be there.
[Dmitri, in English] What do you mean?
[in English] This.
‪[dramatic stinging]
[in English] What the hell?
Why do you have a hole in your window?
[music swells]
[music fades]
Sorry, Boss Red.
You don't want to do this anymore?
You want out?
Won't you regret the large amount of money
you would make today?
Boss, maybe he's richer than us.
Looks like he's bragging already.
[ominous music playing]
Don't tease him.
Paldo wants to change his life.
Why don't we let him?
Don't worry, it's okay.
But we still have something to discuss.
Thank you, boss.
All right.
Boss, you let him go?
[sniffs]
I just gave him a head start.
So, you can enjoy.
[foreboding music playing]
[Mongki, in English] Yes, boss.
[music fades]
[Samir, in English]
I am not a quitter, Ms. Audrey.
[in English] Be ready for Samir. [smirks]
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Excuse me, sir.
[in English] Yes?
[in English] The Sokolov brothers
who attended the summit are impostors.
[in English] Are you sure?
[in English] I am sure, sir.
[in English] I knew it.
[in English] I felt there was
something wrong about this man.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] We may have a problem.
[in English] We have been compromised.
[in English] Tell the guests
to leave right now.
[in English] Where's the ambassador?
[in English] What's that?
- [music swells]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
Why-- Why did you do that?!
Shh.
[in English] Check every floor.
[in English] I'll go to the ambassador.
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[in English] Go.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[in English] Dad? Help!
[in English] Help!
[in English] Ambassador!
[thuds]
[machine whirring]
[ominous music playing]
[in English] Ambassador!
[tense music playing]
[Audrey, in English] Help, help!
- [in English] Ambassador! Ambassador!
- [Audrey, in English] Help!
- [in English] Help, help my dad.
- Audrey.
[in English] Check on them!
Call the medic!
[Audrey gasps]
[machine clanging]
[tense music playing]
[device blipping]
[blipping ends, swoosh]
[in English] Dad. Please help--
Please help him.
[Audrey grunts]
[Audrey, in English] Get him.
[glass screeches]
[device blips]
[music fades]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
- [radio static]
- [in English] Check on the perimeter.
[in English] We have a breach.
[in English] I repeat,
we have a security breach!
- [in English] Check the perimeter!
- [Audrey, indistinct]
[pensive music playing]
[Audrey mutters]
- [in English] You…
- [Audrey, in English] Wake up.
[in English] What happened here?
[unsettling music playing]
[in English] Uh, s-s-some--
Some guy in a mask
jumped over the kitchen counter.
He ran and hit my dad
and the ambassador over the head and…
he climbed out the hole in the window.
[in English] But you're okay, Ms. Audrey.
[in English] You didn't call for help.
[in English] You didn't scream.
Nothing, you did nothing.
- [music fades]
- [in English] I was in shock.
[in English] And he was holding a gun.
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] He told me not to scream.
[in English] Why didn't he hurt you?
[in English] I don't know!
[in English] Why are you asking me
so many questions?
[in English] Shouldn't you be more worried
about the ambassador and my dad?!
[tense music playing]
[in Russian] I’m not sure.
[in English] Bring her
to the interrogation room.
[rousing music playing]
[in English] Now!
[tense music playing]
[in English] Where are you taking me?
What about my dad?!
[in English] Let go of me!
[in English] Where are we going?!
[music swells]
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
[Atoy] Emerson.
[music fades]
[in English] Mr. Ambassador,
we found you on the floor, unconscious.
[in English] Do you remember anything
that happened to you?
[suspicious music playing]
[in English] Wait.
[device blipping]
[tense music playing]
[in English] It's gone!
[in English] It's not here!
[in English] Samir, alert everybody!
[in English] Hold him!
[in English] An important
piece of information is gone!
[in English] Did you
have something to do with this?!
[in English] No! No, Viktor. No!
[in English] I was struck in the head.
I was out cold!
[in English] I-- I don't know this man.
[in English] I swear!
[in English] Where's my daughter?
[in English] She was here. Wh-Where's--
[in English] She's with me
in another room.
[in English] I have her.
Samir.
[in English] Did you catch the thief?
[in English] No.
[in English] I did not. He got away.
[in English] Who could have done this?
[in English] Someone must have helped him.
Viktor.
[in English] I value our friendship!
[in English] I will never
steal anything from you.
[in English] If you want,
I can help you find this man.
[in English] I know
a very good tracker, a man-hunter.
[tense music playing]
[Paldo] Where's the crew hanging out?
- [music concludes]
- Call them. I'll buy drinks!
Hurry.
Ma'am, can I buy soft drinks?
[friend on the phone] Oh? I thought
you had work with Mongki.
[pensive music playing]
Not anymore.
I quit.
I can't take what they're doing anymore.
[tense music playing]
[friend on the phone]
They just let you go like that?
Paldo, be careful.
Why?
I'm still alive, aren't I?
[music swells]
[ominous music playing]
[exhilarating rock music playing]
[Emerson] Sir Ben?
Sir Ben!
[music fades]
Sir Ben, what happened?
I just went to the bathroom!
- [suspicious music playing]
- Why did you leave me right away? Doc!
Wha-- What happened?
Sir Ben, I'm sorry! Sir Ben!
I'm sorry, if you have kids,
I'll pay their tuition. Just live!
Sir Ben! Sir Ben!
Doc! Doc!
What did he die of?
Patient Reyes had cardiac arrest.
[in English] Cardiac arrest?!
[sobs]
But your companion is still alive.
- I just transferred him to the other side.
- Huh?
Who is this?
- [gasps]
- [sneaky music playing]
Doc, what's going on?
Sir Ben!
Doc!
Why didn't you say so?
You're unbelievable.
I was promising scholarships
to someone else.
[chuckles] Sir Ben.
[doctor] Mr. Laput is fine now.
He just fainted because he's anemic.
But I prescribed something for him.
[sighs]
Jesus!
Just anemia?
- [sighs]
- [sneaky music playing]
Thank you. Thank you, Doc.
My God.
Good thing you're okay, Sir Ben.
[Emerson sighs loudly]
I thought something worse happened.
Wait, wait.
- [music concludes]
- Gosh.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[in English] Hello?
Hello, Emerson! What's up?
[Emerson on the phone] Atoy, jeez!
Thank God. Sir Ben is okay now.
I didn't know this mission
would be this hard.
- [pensive music playing]
- I'll get back to you, okay?
I hope you got what you needed.
[Atoy on the phone]
Don't-- Don't come back.
It's probably chaotic there!
Go straight to the tailoring shop.
Take care of my car, okay?
Okay. Okay, okay.
[exhales]
[rousing music playing]
[tense music playing]
He's just around.
Surround him!
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[Mongki] Look over there.
- [grunting]
- [thumping]
[groaning and grunting]
[thumping]
[grunting and groaning]
[upbeat rock music playing]
[thumps, then thuds]
[Mongki] Chase him! Stand up!
[music fades]
[line rings]
[panting, in English] Sir. Bingo.
I got the package.
[Mercado, in English] Move to my location
immediately for turnover.
- [in English] Copy.
- [Mercado, in English] Good job, Padua.
[in English] Oh, okay. To the rally point.
[in English] Okay.
I'll meet you there now, sir.
[in English] Okay. Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[phone rings]
Hello, Miss Cita!
Why did you call?
Emerson, how's your mission?
I can't contact Atoy.
Ah, he's busy, busy.
You won't be able to talk to him.
Weren't you together?
Since I dropped him off,
I haven't seen him.
He told me to go home.
I didn't even feel like
I was in dangerous missions.
He just sent me with an anemic patient
to the hospital, and that was it.
- [quirky music playing]
- So, what do you want to happen?
Miss, of course.
I want it like in action movies.
The ones I see online,
with adrenaline rushes.
This Atoy, the way he sells it to me,
you'd think it was such
an important mission.
He said it was for the country.
But it didn't feel that way to me.
Oh, Emerson.
At least you're safe!
Just wait. That adrenaline rush
you're looking for will come.
Okay. Take care.
Yes, all right.
[T-Bak] Pass right away!
Hey, Gavin! Wait.
[T-Bak, in English] Gavin, my man!
[in English] Long time no see!
- [light music playing]
- [T-Bak] How are you?
[Billy] Busy with his girlfriend.
Karla isn't with you?
[Putoy] I don't know.
She suddenly got mad at us
just because of iced water.
Yes, and we're heading to FO now!
She doesn't show up here anymore!
Let her be!
You've been friends for so long,
and you fight over iced water?
She didn't say anything.
What, are we supposed to guess?
Just understand her.
[phone vibrates]
[in English] Babe?
Yes, we're on later.
I'll pick you up.
[in English] All right. See you.
[music stops]
[bright music playing]
Karla?
- [Putoy] Did you see her?
- [T-Bak] No, nothing.
I'll go ahead, bros.
- [Gavin] See you.
- Take care!
[in English] Dad? Dad!
[Dmitri, in English] Yes.
- [in English] Are you okay? [sighs]
- [in English] I'm fine.
You, were you hurt by the thief?
[in English] No, no.
[in English] But do they have
any leads who did it?
[Dmitri sighs]
None.
[in English] But can you imagine?
He made a hole in the window,
entered and exited from the ninth floor.
[in English] To go through that effort,
it must be a highly skilled thief.
- [suspicious music playing]
- [Dmitri scoffs]
They even suspected me, as an accomplice.
So, they held me in the office.
I want to help them catch the thief.
There's national data on the laptop
that was stolen.
[in English] Dad,
it's none of our business.
And besides, there's nothing
you can do about it anyway.
[sighs]
I just thought,
maybe Atoy could help us.
[in English] Since he's a tracker.
[sighs]
After you told him to stay away from me?
[in English] I don't think so, Dad.
[music swells]
[music fades]
[mid-tempo rock music playing]
- [in English] Boss.
- Oh?
Can I borrow your motorbike?
Borrow my motorbike?
Are you crazy?
[grunts]
[Atoy] Sorry, bro.
[in English] Matter of national security.
Can I borrow the helmet too?
[ominous music playing]
Boss, there!
- He passed here!
- Follow him, quick!
[upbeat rock music playing]
[music swells]
[tense music playing]
- Paldo.
- [panting]
Paldo, what happened to you?
Emerson, help me. Someone's chasing me.
- Why? What happened to you?
- Help me.
[engine running]
[panting]
[Mongki] Where did he go?!
- Point it out! Where?!
- [gasps]
[gasping]
Wait. Did you rob someone?!
Don't make this a getaway car!
This is Atoy's car!
Someone's going to kill me, Emerson!
Do you understand?!
- Who?
- There! Them!
- [sharp exhale]
- [tense music playing]
Paldo!
[Mongki] You exhausted us!
They're going to kill me!
I know them. That's Red's crew!
Get down from there,
or we'll rain bullets on you!
Paldo, jeez!
Why did you drag me into this?!
I don't want trouble!
I don't want an adrenaline rush.
I'm not a hero!
[Mongki] One, two!
[in English] Atoy, what would you do?!
Two and a half!
Possess me, Atoy!
Okay, I'll just get out
so you won't get involved!
No, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'll handle it. I'll save you.
Put on your seat belt!
Put on your seat belt, then duck!
Duck!
- [grunts]
- [rock music playing]
[screams]
- [laughing]
- Faster! Faster!
- Whoo!
- [growls]
[music swells]
[music fades]
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ In the tangle of the city
You're the timing ♪
♪ When you cut… ♪
[Atoy, in English] Sir.
♪ Like a bubble, like a bubble
Like a bubble ♪
♪ When the cutter knows how to hit ♪
[music swells]
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
[gunshots]
[gasps] They're here!
Leave now. Let me handle this!
No, no!
[Emerson] We're both getting out of here!
[Emerson grunts]
Emerson, you must survive!
You need to tell Atoy the truth!
[Atoy] So, he already knew!
Why is he only telling me now?
I understand. Okay, okay.
Let out all your anger.
But remember, you're not a killer.
There's no legal way for demons like him!
UP NEXT
[T-Bak] There are men
outside Paldo's house!
And they're shooting at his house!
It's Mongki's crew.
- Maybe Red is with them. Move!
- [Emerson] 'Toy, 'Toy, 'Toy, 'Toy, 'Toy!
- Think about this first, Atoy--
- [Munggo] Atoy.
It's Ibyang!
[Munggo] She was taken to the hospital!
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias